export default questions = [
	{
		title: "Data Types",
		questions: [
			{
				points: 100,
				question: "What is the basic data type for non - decimal numerical data?",
				answer: "int (integer)",
			},
			{
				points: 200,
				question:
					"What type of data consists of a set of characters to store text?",
				answer: "String",
			},
			{
				points: 300,
				question: "What data type stores a set of eight 0s and 1s?",
				answer: "byte",
			},
			{
				points: 400,
				question: "What decimal data type has twice the precision of a float?",
				answer: "double",
			},
			{
				points: 500,
				question: "What is the largest numerical non-decimal data type in Java?",
				answer: "long",
			},
		],
	},
	{
		title: "Characters",
		questions: [
			{
				points: 100,
				question: "What character indicates the start of a comment in Python?",
				answer: "#",
			},
			{
				points: 200,
				question:
					"What character represents the highest single-digit value in hexadecimal?",
				answer: "F",
			},
			{
				points: 300,
				question:
					"What character seperates the username from the domain of an email address?",
				answer: "@",
			},
			{
				points: 400,
				question:
					"What character is used to calculate remainder in mathematical equations in code?",
				answer: "%",
			},
			{
				points: 500,
				question:
					"What character is used as an escape sequence to make the next character in a strng behave differently?",
				answer: "\\",
			},
		],
	},
	{
		title: "Code Structures",
		questions: [
			{
				points: 100,
				question: 'What is the four-letter abbreviation for "else if" in Python?',
				answer: "elif",
			},
			{
				points: 200,
				question:
					"Which common case-based branching structure is not present in Python?",
				answer: "Switch",
			},
			{
				points: 300,
				question:
					"Which data structure (in math or in code) does not contain repeat values?",
				answer: "Set",
			},
			{
				points: 400,
				question: "Which data structure contains a list of linked keys and values?",
				answer: "Dictionary",
			},
			{
				points: 500,
				question:
					"What SQL keyword is used to specify a condition that determines which records to output?",
				answer: "WHERE",
			},
		],
	},
	{
		title: "Commands",
		questions: [
			{
				points: 100,
				question:
					"What command is used to leave the current command prompt session?",
				answer: "exit",
			},
			{
				points: 200,
				question: "What command is used to show a list of available commands?",
				answer: "help",
			},
			{
				points: 300,
				question: "What command is used to change directories in command prompt?",
				answer: "cd",
			},
			{
				points: 400,
				question:
					"What command-line interface other than command prompt is built into Windows machines?",
				answer: "Windows Powershell",
			},
			{
				points: 500,
				question: "What command is used to analyze a drive and display its status?",
				answer: "chkdsk",
			},
		],
	},
	{
		title: "Operating Systems",
		questions: [
			{
				points: 100,
				question: "What is the Operating System for mobile devices made by Apple?",
				answer: "iOS",
			},
			{
				points: 200,
				question: "What operating system do Google Chromebooks use?",
				answer: "ChromeOS",
			},
			{
				points: 300,
				question:
					"What predecessor of Linux and macOS was developed by Bell Labs in the early 1970s?",
				answer: "Unix",
			},
			{
				points: 400,
				question:
					"22H2 is the last major update for what popular Operating System that will be supported through October 2025?",
				answer: "Windows 10",
			},
			{
				points: 500,
				question:
					'What popular Linux distribution is named after a Southern African word for "humanity to others"?',
				answer: "Ubuntu",
			},
		],
	},
];
